Wake up America,smell the decay
Corporate vultures circling their prey
Wake up America, smell the decay
The Department of Education's been stripped away
Corporate vultures circling their prey
Billionaires calling all the shots today
The Department of Education's been stripped away
Textbooks burned, teachers purged
Billionaires calling all the shots today
burned,teachers purged
Ignorance praised, knowledge submerged
Textbooks burned, teachers purged
Ignorance praised,knowledge submerged
A calculated plan they've finally unleashed
Ignorance praised, knowledge submerged
To keep the masses dumb and on their knees
A calculated plan they've finally unleashed
keep the masses dumb and on their knees
Education's on the chopping block
To keep the masses dumb and on their knees
Corporate overlords with private stock
Education's on the chopping block
stock
Tearing down what we built up
Corporate overlords with private stock
America's future going bankrupt
Tearing down what we built up
future going bankrupt
Hey! Hey! Hey! (Dumbed down!)
America's future going bankrupt
down!)
Billionaires with their twisted schemes
Hey! Hey! Hey! (Dumbed down!)
Dismantling schools for profit dreams
Billionaires with their twisted schemes
schools for profit dreams
Children left behind, can't compete
Dismantling schools for profit dreams
Children left behind,can't compete
While other nations surge ahead, we retreat
Children left behind, can't compete
While other nations surge ahead,we retreat
They cut the funding, cut the facts
While other nations surge ahead, we retreat
They cut the funding,cut the facts
A generation's future under attack
Critical thinking becomes a crime
As we watch our country's steep decline
Education's on the chopping block
Corporate overlords with private stock
Tearing down what we built up
America's future going bankrupt
Hey! Hey! Hey! (Dumbed down!)
Hey!Hey!Hey!(Dumbed down!)
Hey! Hey! Hey! (Sold out!)
Hey! Hey! Hey! (Dumbed down!)
Hey!Hey!Hey!(Sold out!)
Democracy crumbles when ignorance reigns
Hey! Hey! Hey! (Sold out!)
A population they can easily contain
Democracy crumbles when ignorance reigns
No facts, no science, just propaganda flows
A population they can easily contain
No facts,no science,just propaganda flows
A calculated plan that nobody knows
No facts, no science, just propaganda flows
Public schools shuttered, privatized gain
A calculated plan that nobody knows
schools shuttered,privatized gain
The wealthy get choices, the rest feel the pain
Public schools shuttered, privatized gain
The wealthy get choices,the rest feel the pain
Tech bros and tyrants control what we learn
The wealthy get choices, the rest feel the pain
and tyrants control what we learn
While textbooks and truth get thrown in to burn
Tech bros and tyrants control what we learn
in to burn
Tearing down what we built up
While textbooks and truth get thrown in to burn
what we built up
America's future going bankrupt
Tearing down what we built up
bankrupt
Fight back! (Rise up!)
America's future going bankrupt
Fight back!(Rise up!)
Fight back! (Stand up!)
Fight back! (Rise up!)
(Stand up!)
Our children deserve more than their greed
Fight back! (Stand up!)
Knowledge is power we desperately need
Our children deserve more than their greed